Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 2
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 2
- Box: 54, folder: 13 (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - Item 21: RCA Retirement Plan Group Annuity Application and Payroll Deduction Authority, Publication (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - Item 22: Employee Identification Card, Publication (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - Item 23: Time Card, Publication (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - Item 24: Employee's Request for Change in Records, Publication (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - Item 25: Employee's Withholding Exemption Certificate, Publication (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - Item 26: Employee Form, Publication (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - Item 27: Change in Rate (hourly), Publication (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - Item 28: Change in Occupation, Publication (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - Item 29: Change of Name Form, Publication (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - Item 30: Notice of Change of Address, Publication (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - Item 31: Changes of Address, Publication (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - Item 32: Personnel Security Questionnaire, Publication (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - Item 33: Employment Requisition (Regular), Publication (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - Item 34: Physical Examination Record, Publication (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - Item 35: Notice of Employment, Publication (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - Item 36: Radio Corporation of America: RCA Victor Division, Publication (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - Item 37: Standard Procedure Instructions, Publication (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - Item 38: RCA Victor Division Personnel Department Organization, Publication (Box 54, Folder 13)
    September 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 39: Mechanical Engineers in Electronics?, Publication (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - Item 40: Employment Application, Publication (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - Item 41: Referral and Report: Pre-Replacement Health Status Examination, Publication (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - Item 42: Qualification Record, Publication (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - Item 43: Analysis of the Acceptance, Readability, and Content of RCA Victor Publications, Publication (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - Item 44: Working in Research at RCA, Publication (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - Item 45: Application for Employment, Publication (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - Item 46: Federation Des Industries Belges, Publication (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - Item 47: L'Action Des Communautes en Matiere de Readaptation et de Reeducation Professionnelles, Publication (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - Item 48: Notice of Employment, Publication (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - Item 49: RCA Retirement Plan Group Annuity Application and Payroll Deduction Authority, Publication (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - Item 50: Employee's Withholding Exemption Certificate, Publication (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - Item 51: Changes of Address Form, Publication (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - Item 52: Instrucations for Completing P.S.Q. Forms, Publication (Box 54, Folder 13)
- Box: 54, folder: 14 (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: RCA: What it is, What it does, Publication (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - Item 2: RCA Manufacturing and Service Divisions, Publication (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - Item 3: Channels of Contact Chart, Publication (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - Item 4: Electrons at Work--The Story of RCA Victor, Publication (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - Item 5: The Delaware Valleyblends tradition and tomorrow in a life that's inviting, Publication (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - Item 6: The Army Micro-Module Program: Highlights of Progress, Publication (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - Item 7: Opportunities Unlimited: SURFCOM/Surface Communications Department, Publication (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - Item 8: Your Guide to RCA: What it isWhat it doesWhat it makes, Publication (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - Item 9: Patterns of Progress in military and industrial electronics, Publication (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - Item 10: RCA: what it is--what it does, Publication (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - Item 11: 33 Years of Pioneering and Progress, Publication (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - Item 12: Wisdom: The Magazine of Knowledge and Education, Publication (Box 54, Folder 14)
- Box: 54, folder: 15 (Box 54, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Report to Employees 1951, Publication (Box 54, Folder 15)
  - Item 2: RCA Family News: Christmas Issue 1954, Publication (Box 54, Folder 15)
  - Item 3: Radio Corporation of America: Annual Report 1960, Publication (Box 54, Folder 15)
  - Item 4: RCA: what it iswhat it does, Publication (Box 54, Folder 15)
  - Item 5: Engineers Digest, Publication (Box 54, Folder 15)
    January-February 1954. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Engineers Digest, Publication (Box 54, Folder 15)
    November-December 1954. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Radio Age, Publication (Box 54, Folder 15)
    October 1954. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: ThinkSuggestCollect...We Did!, Publication (Box 54, Folder 15)
  - Item 9: Your Ideas Can Earn You $$ at RCA, Publication (Box 54, Folder 15)
  - Item 10: RCA Employee Suggestion Plan, Publication (Box 54, Folder 15)
  - Item 11: Radio Corporation of America: Annual Report 1962, Publication (Box 54, Folder 15)
- Box: 54, folder: 16 (Box 54, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Master Agreement between Radio Corporation of America and Radio Communications Assemblers Union, Inc., Publication (Box 54, Folder 16)
  - Item 2: Master Agreement between Radio Corporation of America and Radio Communications Assemblers Union, Inc., Publication (Box 54, Folder 16)
  - Item 3: Constitution and By-Laws of the Association of Professional Engineering Personnel, Publication (Box 54, Folder 16)
    January 1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Constitution and By-Laws of the Association of Professional Engineering Personnel, Publication (Box 54, Folder 16)
- Box: 54, folder: 17 (Box 54, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: You and MTP, Publication (Box 54, Folder 17)
  - Item 2: If your aim is advancement your best opportunities are with RCA Service Company, Publication (Box 54, Folder 17)
  - Item 3: TV Broadcast Field Engineers, Publication (Box 54, Folder 17)
- Box: 54, folder: 18 (Box 54, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Manual of Hiring Procedures, Publication (Box 54, Folder 18)
  - Item 2: Handbook for Railway Express Employes, Publication (Box 54, Folder 18)
- Box: 54, folder: 19 (Box 54, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Supervisory Notes, Publication (Box 54, Folder 19)
  - Item 2: You and the Press, Publication (Box 54, Folder 19)
  - Item 3: Supervisory Notes, Publication (Box 54, Folder 19)
- Box: 54, folder: 20 (Box 54, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Business Week, Publication (Box 54, Folder 20)
    December 8, 1962. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Railway Age Weekly, Publication (Box 54, Folder 20)
    January 28, 1963. Item is in English.
- Box: 54, folder: 21 (Box 54, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: It's Only Your Job, Publication (Box 54, Folder 21)
- Box: 54, folder: 22 (Box 54, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Another Nine Years of Teamwork, Publication (Box 54, Folder 22)
  - Item 2: The Future of Cities, Publication (Box 54, Folder 22)
  - Item 3: Our Rail Rights, Publication (Box 54, Folder 22)
- Box: 54, folder: 23 (Box 54, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Railroad Marketing, Publication (Box 54, Folder 23)
- Box: 54, folder: 24 (Box 54, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Raymond International Inc. Annual Report 1968, Publication (Box 54, Folder 24)
- Box: 54, folder: 25 (Box 54, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: The Purina Salesman's Job, Publication (Box 54, Folder 25)
- Box: 54, folder: 26 (Box 54, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Meet Ralston Purina, Publication (Box 54, Folder 26)
- Box: 54, folder: 27 (Box 54, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: The Reading: Building a Modern Railroad, Publication (Box 54, Folder 27)
- Box: 54, folder: 28 (Box 54, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Real Estate's Labor Problem, Publication (Box 54, Folder 28)
  - Item 2: A Report, Publication (Box 54, Folder 28)
  - Item 3: The Realty Advisory Board on Labor Relations, Incorporated, Publication (Box 54, Folder 28)
  - Item 4: The Realty Advisory Board on Labor Relations, Incorporated, Publication (Box 54, Folder 28)
  - Item 5: Profit or Loss?, Publication (Box 54, Folder 28)
  - Item 6: Realty Advisory Board on Labor Relations, Incorporated, Publication (Box 54, Folder 28)
- Box: 54, folder: 29 (Box 54, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Reington Reporter, Publication (Box 54, Folder 29)
    March 16, 1978. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Labor and National Defense, Publication (Box 54, Folder 29)
    By William Green. April 2, 1941. Item is in English.
- Box: 55, folder: 1 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Remington Rand: Employees Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Ideas Report, Publication (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Employees Suggestion News Bulletin, Publication (Box 55, Folder 1)
    December 1949. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Employees Suggestion News Bulletin, Publication (Box 55, Folder 1)
    October 1949. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Employees Suggestion News Bulletin, Publication (Box 55, Folder 1)
    September 1949. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Employees Suggestion News Bulletin, Publication (Box 55, Folder 1)
    August 1949. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Employees Suggestion News Bulletin, Publication (Box 55, Folder 1)
    June 1949. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Employees Suggestion News Bulletin, Publication (Box 55, Folder 1)
    April 1949. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Employees Suggestion News Bulletin, Publication (Box 55, Folder 1)
    May 1949. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Remington Rand Employee Suggestion Plan: Manual of Procedure, Publication (Box 55, Folder 1)
- Box: 55, folder: 2 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: About You and Remington Rand, Publication (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Application for Employment, Publication (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Termination Interview, Publication (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Indoctrination Interview, Publication (Box 55, Folder 2)
- Box: 55, folder: 3 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: You and Remington Rand, Publication (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: "Truth will Out", Publication (Box 55, Folder 3)
- Box: 55, folder: 4 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: $$$ for your ideas, Publication (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: $$$ for your ideas, Publication (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Ideas, Publication (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: News Letter Suggestion Plan, Publication (Box 55, Folder 4)
    January 1950. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Ideas at Tonawanda, Publication (Box 55, Folder 4)
- Box: 55, folder: 5 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Cost and Waste Saving Ideas, Publication (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Disciplinary Standards Policy, Publication (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Personnel Procedure Forms, Publication (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: Organization Chart, Publication (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: Personnel Record, Publication (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: Employee Handbook, Publication (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Item 7: Instructions for Completing Starting Papers and Reporting to Work, Publication (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Item 8: Acts of Conduct Where Disciplinary Action Shall Be Taken Before Discharge, Publication (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Item 9: Exit Interview, Publication (Box 55, Folder 5)
- Box: 55, folder: 6 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Annal Report 1952, Publication (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Annual Report for 1950, Publication (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: Republic Digest, Publication (Box 55, Folder 6)
- Box: 55, folder: 7 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: For Release: GOP Leadership Group Calls for Social Security Benefit Increase, Publication (Box 55, Folder 7)
- Box: 55, folder: 8 (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: You as a part of Republic, Publication (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: You as a part of Republic, Publication (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: Republic Steel: Environment for Success, Publication (Box 55, Folder 8)
- Box: 55, folder: 9 (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: The Steel Industry--It's Growth and Problems, Publication (Box 55, Folder 9)
    By E. M. Richards. April 7, 1950. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Breaking Through the Communications Barrier, Publication (Box 55, Folder 9)
    By C. M. White. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Of, By and For the Government, Publication (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Item 4: Meet the Press, Publication (Box 55, Folder 9)
    June 28, 1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Basic Safety Instructions for all Employees, Publication (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Item 6: 1972 Annual Report, Publication (Box 55, Folder 9)
- Box: 55, folder: 10 (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Annual Report for 1951, Publication (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Item 2: Annual Report 1964, Publication (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Item 3: Annual Report 1963, Publication (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Item 4: Annual Report 1962, Publication (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Item 5: Annual Report 1961, Publication (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Item 6: Annual Report 1968, Publication (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Item 7: A Visit to the Buffalo District Plant, Publication (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Item 8: Annual Report 1969, Publication (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Item 9: Annual Report 1971, Publication (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Item 10: Annual Report 1973, Publication (Box 55, Folder 10)
- Box: 55, folder: 11 (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Proceedings Annual Meeting 1951, Publication (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - Item 2: Two-Year Progress Report, Publication (Box 55, Folder 11)
- Box: 55, folder: 12 (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: How a Hospital Developed Its Own Personnel Manual, Publication (Box 55, Folder 12)
- Box: 55, folder: 13 (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Labor Report, Publication (Box 55, Folder 13)
    January 21, 1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: How to Keep Profits Ahead of Sales, Publication (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - Item 3: Taxation Report, Publication (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - Item 4: Research Institute Report, Publication (Box 55, Folder 13)
- Box: 55, folder: 14 (Box 55, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Letter to Miss Eckert, Publication (Box 55, Folder 14)
    January 28, 1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: What is Research Institute Membership?, Publication (Box 55, Folder 14)
  - Item 3: Your Part in the Executive Membership Program, Publication (Box 55, Folder 14)
- Box: 55, folder: 15 (Box 55, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Annual Report for the year ended June 30, 1955, Publication (Box 55, Folder 15)
- Box: 55, folder: 16 (Box 55, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: The Retirement Advisor: Your Monthly Newsletter, Publication (Box 55, Folder 16)
  - Item 2: Retirement Advisor: Your Monthly Newsletter, Publication (Box 55, Folder 16)
    June 1984. Item is in English.
- Box: 55, folder: 17 (Box 55, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Summary of RAI Services, Publication (Box 55, Folder 17)
  - Item 2: Letter, Publication (Box 55, Folder 17)
- Box: 55, folder: 18 (Box 55, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: It's an Idea from Dartnell, Publication (Box 55, Folder 18)
- Box: 55, folder: 19 (Box 55, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: 1959 Report to Revere Employees, Publication (Box 55, Folder 19)
  - Item 2: A Report to Revere Employees for the year ended December 31, 1955, Publication (Box 55, Folder 19)
  - Item 3: The Revere Reporter, Publication (Box 55, Folder 19)
  - Item 4: The Revere Reporter, Publication (Box 55, Folder 19)
  - Item 5: 1958 Report to Revere Employees, Publication (Box 55, Folder 19)
  - Item 6: The Revere Report, Publication (Box 55, Folder 19)
  - Item 7: The Revere Report, Publication (Box 55, Folder 19)
  - Item 8: The Revere Reporter, Publication (Box 55, Folder 19)
  - Item 9: The Revere Reporter, Publication (Box 55, Folder 19)
  - Item 10: 1957 Report to Revere Employees, Publication (Box 55, Folder 19)
- Box: 55, folder: 20 (Box 55, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Paul Revere: Pioneer, Industrialist, Publication (Box 55, Folder 20)
  - Item 2: The Spirit of Paul Revere--a Glorious Heritage for American Industry, Publication (Box 55, Folder 20)
  - Item 3: Let's Get the Record Straight, Publication (Box 55, Folder 20)
    By C. Donald Dallas. Item is in English.
- Box: 55, folder: 21 (Box 55, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: The Revere Job Reporter, Publication (Box 55, Folder 21)
  - Item 2: Revere and Your Future, Publication (Box 55, Folder 21)
  - Item 3: Partners in Revere, Publication (Box 55, Folder 21)
- Box: 55, folder: 22 (Box 55, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Rexall Drug and Chemical Company Annual Report 1966, Publication (Box 55, Folder 22)
  - Item 2: Rexall Drug and Chemical Company Annual Report 1965, Publication (Box 55, Folder 22)
- Box: 55, folder: 23 (Box 55, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Welcome to the General Sales Office, Publication (Box 55, Folder 23)
  - Item 2: Reynolds Aluminum and the company that makes it, Publication (Box 55, Folder 23)
- Box: 55, folder: 24 (Box 55, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: General Labor Relations Agreement between Reynolds Metals Company, Inc. and Local Affiliated Labor Unions, Publication (Box 55, Folder 24)
- Box: 55, folder: 25 (Box 55, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Your CareerOur Business, Publication (Box 55, Folder 25)
  - Item 2: Vacation with Pay Plan for Salaried Employees other than the Field Sales Force, Publication (Box 55, Folder 25)
  - Item 3: Jury Service Plan for Full-Time Hourly-Rated and Piecework Regular Employees of R.J. Tobacco Co., Publication (Box 55, Folder 25)
  - Item 4: Parking Regulations for Employees of R.J. Reynolds Tobacco Co. in the Winston-Salem, NC Area, Publication (Box 55, Folder 25)
  - Item 5: In Recognition of Long Service, Publication (Box 55, Folder 25)
  - Item 6: Your Engineering CareerOur Business, Publication (Box 55, Folder 25)
  - Item 7: Your CareerOur Business, Publication (Box 55, Folder 25)
  - Item 8: Selling as a Career at RJR, Publication (Box 55, Folder 25)
  - Item 9: Your Service Award Program, Publication (Box 55, Folder 25)
  - Item 10: Your CareerOur Business, Publication (Box 55, Folder 25)
- Box: 55, folder: 26 (Box 55, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Annual Report 1965, Publication (Box 55, Folder 26)
  - Item 2: Annual Report 1959, Publication (Box 55, Folder 26)
  - Item 3: Letter to Employee, Publication (Box 55, Folder 26)
  - Item 4: Letter to Employee, Publication (Box 55, Folder 26)
  - Item 5: Suggestion Plan for Eligible Employees of R.J. Reynolds Tobacco Comopany, Publication (Box 55, Folder 26)
  - Item 6: Suggestion of the Month!, Publication (Box 55, Folder 26)
  - Item 7: Caravan, Publication (Box 55, Folder 26)
  - Item 8: Annual Report 1967, Publication (Box 55, Folder 26)
  - Item 9: Management Bulletin, Publication (Box 55, Folder 26)
    January 11, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Your Share in the RJR Progress, Publication (Box 55, Folder 26)
  - Item 11: Caravan, Publication (Box 55, Folder 26)
  - Item 12: Caravan, Publication (Box 55, Folder 26)
  - Item 13: R.J. Reynolds Industries, Publication (Box 55, Folder 26)
  - Item 14: Letter to Stockholders, Publication (Box 55, Folder 26)
    July 20, 1972. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Annual Report 1971 R.J. Reynolds Industries, Inc., Publication (Box 55, Folder 26)
  - Item 16: R.J. Reynolds Tobacco Company: Your CareerOur Business, Publication (Box 55, Folder 26)
  - Item 17: Preparing for a Second Century of Progress, Publication (Box 55, Folder 26)
  - Item 18: Profile in sales., Publication (Box 55, Folder 26)
  - Item 19: Research & Project Development, Publication (Box 55, Folder 26)
  - Item 20: Short Puffs, Publication (Box 55, Folder 26)
- Box: 55, folder: 27 (Box 55, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Management Bulletin, Publication (Box 55, Folder 27)
    December 9, 1960. Item is in English.
- Box: 55, folder: 28 (Box 55, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: A Short History of R.J. Reynolds Tobacco Company, Publication (Box 55, Folder 28)
  - Item 2: A History of R.J. Reynolds Tobacco Company, Publication (Box 55, Folder 28)
  - Item 3: Tobacco as a Crop, Publication (Box 55, Folder 28)
  - Item 4: Facts Concerning Our Cigarettes, Publication (Box 55, Folder 28)
  - Item 5: R.J. Reynolds Tobacco Company, Publication (Box 55, Folder 28)
- Box: 55, folder: 29 (Box 55, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Labor, Publication (Box 55, Folder 29)
- Box: 55, folder: 30 (Box 55, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Rhode Island Temporary Disability Insurance Act and Employment Security Act, Publication (Box 55, Folder 30)
  - Item 2: Labor, Publication (Box 55, Folder 30)
  - Item 3: Workmen's Compensation Commission: Rules and Regulations, Publication (Box 55, Folder 30)
- Box: 55, folder: 31 (Box 55, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: Rating Forms, Publication (Box 55, Folder 31)
  - Item 2: Personnel Forms, Publication (Box 55, Folder 31)
- Box: 55, folder: 32 (Box 55, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: Handbook for Employees of the Richardson Company, Publication (Box 55, Folder 32)
- Box: 55, folder: 33 (Box 55, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: Working Together at Riegel, Publication (Box 55, Folder 33)
- Box: 55, folder: 34 (Box 55, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: Copy of Current Contract between Ritter Company, Inc. and District 6, Publication (Box 55, Folder 34)
- Box: 55, folder: 35 (Box 55, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: Ritter Pfaudler Today, Publication (Box 55, Folder 35)
- Box: 55, folder: 36 (Box 55, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: A Rational Route to Peace and Prosperity in Our Time, Publication (Box 55, Folder 36)
    By James Gordon Roberts. Item is in English.
- Box: 55, folder: 37 (Box 55, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: Hand Book for Employees of the Perry and Mt. Morris Plants, Publication (Box 55, Folder 37)
- Box: 55, folder: 38 (Box 55, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: Wage Agreement Booklet, Publication (Box 55, Folder 38)
- Box: 55, folder: 39 (Box 55, Folder 39)
  - Item 1: Agreement Entered Into Between Rochester Commercial Printers and Rochester Printing Crafts Union, Publication (Box 55, Folder 39)
- Box: 55, folder: 40 (Box 55, Folder 40)
  - Item 1: RG&E News, Publication (Box 55, Folder 40)
    September-October 1967. Item is in English.
- Box: 55, folder: 41 (Box 55, Folder 41)
  - Item 1: Power and Progress in the Genesee Valley, Publication (Box 55, Folder 41)
- Box: 55, folder: 42 (Box 55, Folder 42)
  - Item 1: The ABC's of Rockbesto's for salaried employees, Publication (Box 55, Folder 42)
  - Item 2: Kinks: What Every Rockbestos Employee Should Kow, Publication (Box 55, Folder 42)
- Box: 55, folder: 43 (Box 55, Folder 43)
  - Item 1: Rockbestos Hourglass, Publication (Box 55, Folder 43)
    April 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Rockbestos Hourglass, Publication (Box 55, Folder 43)
  - Item 3: Rockbestos Hourglass, Publication (Box 55, Folder 43)
  - Item 4: Rockbestos, Publication (Box 55, Folder 43)
- Box: 55, folder: 44 (Box 55, Folder 44)
  - Item 1: The President's Review from the Rockerfeller Foundation Annual Report 1959, Publication (Box 55, Folder 44)
- Box: 55, folder: 45 (Box 55, Folder 45)
  - Item 1: Statement of the Rockefeller Foundation and the General Education Board, Publication (Box 55, Folder 45)
  - Item 2: Rockefeller Foundation Grants, Publication (Box 55, Folder 45)
- Box: 55, folder: 46 (Box 55, Folder 46)
  - Item 1: Rules and Instructions Governing the Operation of Railroad Radio Communication System, Publication (Box 55, Folder 46)
    August 1, 1956. Item is in English.
- Box: 55, folder: 47 (Box 55, Folder 47)
  - Item 1: The Larc in Vietnam, Publication (Box 55, Folder 47)
    July-August 1966. Item is in English.
- Box: 55, folder: 48 (Box 55, Folder 48)
  - Item 1: Here's More Rogers, Publication (Box 55, Folder 48)
- Box: 55, folder: 49 (Box 55, Folder 49)
  - Item 1: Welcome to Rogers, Publication (Box 55, Folder 49)
- Box: 55, folder: 50 (Box 55, Folder 50)
  - Item 1: Nineteenth Annual Report, Publication (Box 55, Folder 50)
- Box: 56, folder: 1 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: The Roper Public Opinion Research Center 1962-1963 Bulletin, Publication (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: The Roper Public Opinion Research Center at Williams College 1960 Bulletin, Publication (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: The Roper Public Opinion Research Center, Publication (Box 56, Folder 1)
- Box: 56, folder: 2 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Bank of the Seven Merchants, Publication (Box 56, Folder 2)
- Box: 56, folder: 3 (Box 56, Folder 3)